[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who falls in love with the monster in the comedy film Young Frankenstein?", "correct_answer": "Elizabeth", "incorrect_answers": ["Inga", "no one", "Inspector Kemp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which TV series did American rapper Ice-T make his television debut?", "correct_answer": "Players", "incorrect_answers": ["Law Order SVU", "The District", "Thieves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Similarly to spinach, this fruit, called petia in Spain, contains plenty of iron.", "correct_answer": "Watermelon", "incorrect_answers": ["Mango", "Avocado", "Banana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sean Connery and two 007 enemies participated in The Longest Day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The genus to which yarrow belongs is named after this mythological Greek hero, who allegedly used yarrow to treat soldiers wounds.", "correct_answer": "Achilles", "incorrect_answers": ["Hercules", "Paris", "Odysseus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The phase Greatest thing since sliced bread derived from a Wonder Bread advertising campaign.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All the listed actresses were nominees for the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actress for 1987. Name the lucky winner.", "correct_answer": "Madonna for Whos That Girl?", "incorrect_answers": ["Debra Sandlund for Tough Guys Dont Dance", "Lorraine Gary for Jaws: The Revenge", "Sharon Stone for Allan Quatermain and the Lost City of Gold"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the traditional South African meal Boerewors mean in Afrikaans?", "correct_answer": "Farmers sausage", "incorrect_answers": ["Bulls horns", "Fish scales", "Sows intestines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this US state it is illegal to tattoo an unconscious person.", "correct_answer": "Texas", "incorrect_answers": ["Nevada", "Florida", "California"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie about an alien visiting our planet starred Jeff Bridges, Karen Allen and Robert Phalen.", "correct_answer": "Starman", "incorrect_answers": ["K-Pax", "Close Encounters of the 3rd Kind", "E.T."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the proverb:\nPoets are born, ________.", "correct_answer": "...not made.", "incorrect_answers": ["...but thats not for sure.", "..., long live the poets!", "...but can also be made."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saint Paul is the capital city of what US state?", "correct_answer": "Minnesota", "incorrect_answers": ["Missouri", "Mississippi", "None of these"]}]